const e={sections:[{header:{text:"Choose the correct option"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"Who has eaten everything in the fridge?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Vanya has.",2:"Vanya did.",3:"Vanya do.",4:"Vanya does."}},{type:"test",question:"Somebody called me at 5 a.m.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who called you at 5 a.m.",2:"Who did call?",3:"Who call?",4:"What did called you?"}},{type:"test",question:"I am an English teacher.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who is an English teacher?",2:"What are you?",3:"Who an English teacher?",4:"Who an English teacher is?"}},{type:"test",question:"They will do some shopping tomorrow.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who will do some shopping tomorrow?",2:"What will do some shopping tomorrow?",3:"Who does some shopping tomorrow?",4:"They will what do?"}},{type:"test",question:"A new pencil is in my bag.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"What is in my bag?",2:"Whose bag is it?",3:"What bag is it?",4:"What pencil in my bag?"}},{type:"test",question:"What happened last week?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"An accident did.",2:"An accident was.",3:"An accident had.",4:"An accident."}},{type:"test",question:"Cristina loves sausages.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who loves sausages?",2:"What loves Cristina?",3:"What Cristina is?",4:"When loves sausages?"}},{type:"test",question:"Who was reading a newspaper when Mother came?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Her son was.",2:"Her son did.",3:"Her son is.",4:"Mother was."}},{type:"test",question:"The child became a very beautiful girl.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who became a very beautiful girl?",2:"What became a very beautiful girl?",3:"Became what?",4:"A very beautiful girl who become?"}},{type:"test",question:"I know the right answer.",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who knows the right answer?",2:"Who does know the right answer?",3:"Who the right answer knows?",4:"What is the right answer?"}}]},{header:{text:"Choose the correct option"},exercises:[{type:"test",question:"Что делает меня счастливым?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"What makes me happy?",2:"What does make me happy?",3:"Who does make me happy?",4:"What make me happy?"}},{type:"test",question:"Кто поет песню на английском языке?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who does sing a song in English?",2:"What sing a song in English?",3:"Who did sing a song in English?",4:"Who sings a song in English?"}},{type:"test",question:"Что спасло твою жизнь?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"What saved your life?",2:"Who saved your life?",3:"Who you save your life?",4:"What did save your life?"}},{type:"test",question:"Кто твой первый учитель?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who is your first teacher?",2:"What is your first teacher?",3:"Who your first teacher is?",4:"What your first teacher is?"}},{type:"test",question:"Кто было рядом с тобой, когда это случилось?",rightAnswerIds:["1"],answers:{1:"Who was near you when that happened?",2:"Who did be near you when that happened?",3:"What happened?",4:"Who was there?"}}]}]};export{e as default};
